It's never too late to risk it all.
Jerry & Marge Go Large is a comedy, drama film directed by David Frankel.
The remarkable true story of how retiree Jerry Selbee discovers a mathematical loophole in the Massachusetts lottery and, with
the help of his wife, Marge, wins $27 million dollars and uses the money to revive their small Michigan town.
Jerry Selbee, played by Bryan Cranston.
Marge Selbee, played by Annette Bening.
Bill, played by Rainn Wilson.
Steve, played by Larry Wilmore.
Howard, played by Michael McKean.
Doug, played by Jake McDorman.
Jerry & Marge Go Large is a 2022 American comedy-drama film
directed by David Frankel and written by Brad Copeland.
Based on Jason Fagone's 2018 HuffPost article of the same name, the film, which is
based on a true story, stars Bryan Cranston and Annette Bening.
The film premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival on June 15, 2022,
and was released on Paramount+ on June 17, 2022.
The film explores themes of small town, michigan,
mathematics, massachusetts, harvard university.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.